welcome to episode number 310 of
欢迎来到第310集
category five technology TV it's Tuesday
第五类技术电视是星期二
the 27th of August 2013 nice to see ya
2013年8月 27 日很高兴见到 你
hey folks well I've got some great
嘿伙计好我有一些伟大的
things on the newsroom right such as a
新闻编辑部右侧的内容 如a
Raspberry Pi powered teddy bear set a
树莓派动力泰迪熊设置 了一个
freefall record for teddy bears
泰迪熊自由落体记录
everywhere Wow
到处哇
Amazon experienced more downtime on the
亚马逊 经历了更多的停机时间 的
weekend and this time it affected
周末，这一次它受到影响
several high-profile clients including
包括几个高调的客户
Netflix and Instagram oh I know bad news
Netflix 和Instagram哦，我知道坏消息
a web designer is receiving tweets like
一位网页设计师正在接收 类似 tweets的消息
it's 1867 hmm I'm not sure how to take
这是1867年嗯，我不 知道如何 采取
that one windows 8 benchmarks are banned
那一个 Windows 8基准被禁止
from HW BOTS benchmark records due to a
来自HW BOTS的基准测试记录归因于a
time issue with Windows 8 oh dear stick
时间问题与Windows 8 哦亲爱的棒
around Kuusisto
Kuusisto周围
or they're sorry not these shows these
或者他们很抱歉没有这些显示这些
stories are coming up later in the show
故事稍后会在节目中出现
it's only one show Hey tonight exciting
这只是一个节目 嘿 今晚令人兴奋
stuff the age-old question is going to
这个古老的问题将会 发生
be answered how does Robbie get those
被回答如何罗比得到这些
ring looking things on his desktop we're
在他的桌面上看着 我们的 东西
gonna be looking at getting desktop
要寻找在 获得桌面
widgets on your Linux computer so don't
你的Linux电脑上的小工具， 所以不要
go anywhere we're gonna learn all about
去任何我们要学习的地方
it tonight as well we've got your
它今晚以及我们已经得到了你的
questions join us in the chatroom
问题在聊天室中加入我们
category-five on freenode we'll be right
freenode上的第五类我们是对的
back after this this is category five
在此之后这是 第五类
technology TV
技术电视
at eco alkaline z' we believe you should
在生态碱z 我们相信你 应该
be able to trust your batteries not just
不仅能够 信任你的电池
here but here here and here but with one
这里， 但在这里，在这里，但有一个
exception you should also be able to
异常你也应该能够
trust your batteries here eco alkaline
相信你的电池在这里生态碱性
zuv the world's first and only certified
zuv是世界上第一个也是唯一一个获得认证的
carbon neutral battery manufactured to
碳中性电池制造
the highest standards of recycling and
回收的最高标准，
quality without any trace amounts of
质量没有任何痕量的
harmful chemicals like mercury lead or
有害的化学物质， 如汞 铅或 汞
cadmium Eco outlines provide performance
镉Eco概述提供性能
the rivals leading national alkaline
领先全国碱性的竞争对手
battery brands at a comparable price
可比价格的电池品牌
find out more about the Eco alkaline
了解 更多 关于 生态碱
difference eco alkaline scum this is
这是不同的生态碱性 废渣
category 5 technology TV so good to have
第5类技术电视这么好 有
you here hey don't forget we've got a
你在这里嘿，别忘了我们 有一个
mobile website go there m dot dot v dot
移动网站去那里 点dot点
TV if you've got your mobile phone your
电视， 如果你有你的手机
smartphone your ipod whatever you have
智能手机 你的 iPod，无论你有什么
your tablet
平板电脑
well gadgets any of those cool gadgets
以及那些酷玩意的小玩意
all you gotta do is scan that code go to
你 要做 的 是扫描代码转到
Emma camp five dot TV and you'll have
艾玛阵营 五点电视，你会有
access to some really cool features
访问一些非常酷的功能
they're just designed specifically for
他们只是专门设计的
you that sounds very cool and category
你听起来很酷，很类似
five TV is a member of the tech podcast
五台 电视是科技 播客 的成员
network if his tech it's here and the
网络如果他的 技术 在这里 和 那里
international association of internet
国际互联网协会
broadcasters excellent hey welcome to
优秀的嘿欢迎广播公司
our newly registered viewers I know on
我 知道 我们新注册的观众
our website
我们的网站
well orange man is now a member of the
还有橙色的人现在是的一员
community so up you just be sending us
社区如此， 你只是送我们
oranges yeah unless that's like a band
橙子是啊，除非这就像一个乐队
thing like it's like the blue man what
就像它像蓝人一样
if he just likes and dances makes rhythm
如果他只是喜欢和跳舞节奏
rhythmic sounds PVC piping some
有节奏的声音PVC管道一些
videotapes we'd like to see it orange
我们希望看到 橙色的 录像带
man your whole group yeah welcome to
男人你的整个团体耶欢迎
Moloch mullet milk
Moloch乌鱼牛奶
Crypt us both correct us by sending us
埋葬我们都寄给 我们 纠正 我们
an email explaining the spelling or the
解释拼写或电子邮件的电子邮件
pronunciation and we'll have to figure
发音 ，我们将不得不 数字
that one out big news for how field this
那一场是如何 领域这个 大新闻
week has just surpassed 250 weeks of
周刚刚超过250周
being a registered viewer here at
作为注册观众在这里
category 5 TV so we present him with the
5 类 电视，所以我们向 他介绍
bronze crown award on our website
铜冠奖在我们的 网站上
category 5 dot TV nice to have him
5类点电视很高兴有他
joining us for so long now how field
现在加入我们这么久的领域如何
reminds us that he actually has been
提醒我们 他确实 是
watching get this since episode 2 oh say
从 第2集开始看这个 哦
you messed up said one missed episode 1
你搞砸说一个错过情节 1
we'll see that's what I had to put out
我们会看到那就是我必须抛弃的东西
episode 1 folks and then the fame that
第1集人 ，然后名声
came from it was just crazy so by
来自它 只是 疯了
episode 2 we had 6 viewers and how field
第二集中，我们有6个观众，以及如何场
was that one new viewer apparently well
那是一位新的观众，显然很好
it's it's we were thinking you know how
这是我们以为你知道如何
did you find this show yeah cuz it was
你有没有发现这个节目啊 cuz它 是
episode 2 right like it's not like we
第2集就像它 不像 我们 一样
had this huge promotional budget and we
有这个巨大的促销预算和我们
were pushing it out over networks and
通过网络推动它
they had television commercials leading
他们以电视广告为主
up to the event well nothing like that
直到事件完全没有像那样
good news travels fast I guess so yeah
好消息快速传播我想是的
so greets to how field thanks for
所以问候如何领域感谢
joining us for so long also active
加入我们这么久 也 积极
viewers on the show we've got quite a
观众在节目中我们已经有很多了
few actually who have been watching for
很少有人一直在关注
250 weeks or more good guy 98 Dave 26
250周以上好人98戴夫26
slipped night star Raj shot of course
当然 滑落的夜星 拉吉 射击
sounds familiar a Jameson has been
听起来很熟悉詹姆森一直
watching for more than 250 weeks
观看超过250 周
Lone Star and our longest active viewer
孤星 和我们最长的活跃观众
our longest standing active viewer is
我们最长的活跃观众是
actually G dog who joins us in the chat
实际上是在聊天中加入我们的G狗
room tonight
今晚的房间
g-dog 1985 underscore nice to have you
g-dog 1985 强调你很高兴
joining us has been registered on the
加入我们已经注册 了
website for the longest time everybody
网站 的时间最长的每个人
which is yeah kind of a neat thing you
这是一种整洁的东西你
find it more about you know all the
发现它更多关于你知道的 所有
people that are registered on our site
在我们的网站 上注册的 人
by going to category 5 TV and you go
通过去5类电视，你走了
into members and registered viewers and
为 会员和注册观众和
it
它
you've got enough fewer points your name
你的名字少得多
is actually gonna show up on that list
实际上 会出现在这张名单上
as well so get yourself registered right
以及让自己注册的权利
away if you've been coming in HoN and
如果你已经进入 HoN和
watching the show and thinking oh I'll
看着节目， 想着哦，我会的
just do it later that's what happened to
稍后 再做 就是发生 了 什么事
how field he's been watching since
自从他一直在观看他的 领域
episode two and he didn't register until
第二集 ，他没有登记，直到
a year later Oh a whole year a whole
一年以后哦整整 一年
year later right like November 11th 12
一年后， 就像11月11 日12
2008 we started the show September of
2008年9月我们开始了演出
2007 so dillydallyin yeah it helps too
2007 所以dillydallyin 是它也有帮助
because who knows 250 weeks from now we
因为谁知道从现在起250周
could be saying greeting your greetings
可以说问候你的问候
to you from our spaceship so
给你从我们的宇宙飞船如此
congratulations are in order
祝贺你
jot in the chatroom says congratulations
在聊天室里写道恭喜
on the marriage and stop yeah so let's
在婚姻 和 停止是啊， 所以让我们
see the bling look at this oh it's
看看这个哦，它是金光闪闪的
blaring in the cameras beautiful day
美丽的一天 ，在相机喧嚣
you're what happened with your
你是你的事情
videographer I just random question
摄影师我只是随机 提问
videographer didn't show up oh well you
摄影师没有出现你哦
always have to have a few wedding blips
总是必须有几个结婚证
in our case it was like wedding
在我们的情况下，它就像婚礼
avalanches but one of the big ones was
雪崩， 但其中一个大的是
the videographer finally got a hold of
摄影师终于得到了保留
me like the day before the wedding and
我喜欢在婚礼的前一天和
said I don't have a ride to bury sorry
说我没有 乘车 埋葬抱歉
no I was like oh well that's good cuz
不，我很喜欢哦，嗯，这是很好 的Cuz
our weddings in berry so yeah so so
我们在浆果的婚礼是 如此的如此
naturally I get a hold of this guy I was
自然我得到这个家伙我 是保持
like who is the geekiest guy I know and
比如谁是我认识的最热心的人
I said I am NOT driving to mainland
我说我不是开车到大陆的
China to pick this guy up yeah sorry I
中国挑这个 家伙耶对不起我
said no no that's okay I said can can we
说不，不，不，我说可以，我们可以
just can we borrow your camcorder right
正好可以借我们在摄像机右侧
and this guy it did more than that well
而这个人做得比这更好
the fact is this is your wedding right
事实是这是你的婚礼权利
you've got you've got to think about
你必须考虑
sound in particular video you can put a
声音，特别是视频，你可以把一个
hand camera in front of somebody and
手在相机某人的前面 和
just say you know please record and go
只是 说你知道请记录下去
and and then you get it home and you
然后你把它带回家和你
realize they can't hear anything
意识到他们听不到任何声音
so music Pro and berry music Pro very
所以音乐 Pro 和 浆果音乐Pro非常
calm they actually pulled through for us
平静他们实际上拉了我们
I give them a call that day and said
我那天给他们打电话说
look krysta from the show they know the
看他们知道的节目krysta
show over there
在那里展示
is getting married tomorrow and has no
要 结婚了，明天，也没有
videographer we need to mic this thing
我们需要录像师将这个东西麦克风
so we actually got a shotgun microphone
所以我们实际上有 一个猎枪麦克风
and I ran a cable like all the way to
我一直在用电缆
the back and push record on a little
稍后回推一下
portable recorder there and everything
便携式录音机和一切
was just flawless so we had a microphone
是完美的，所以我们有一个麦克风
way up at the front right in front of
在前面右 前方
you guys with the with the squirrel tail
你们与松鼠尾巴
windscreen because it was an outdoor
挡风玻璃，因为它是一个室外
wedding and so we had to have a
婚礼，所以我们必须有一个
windscreen and all that running back to
挡风玻璃和所有 跑回去的
the sound all in the size of something
声音都在某种程度上
that fits in your pocket and then just
那适合你的 口袋 ，然后 就是了
the camera on the stand so everything
在支架上的相机如此一切
worked out quite well so when when I was
当时我工作得很好
done recording the wedding got back and
完成录制 婚礼 回来了
the first thing that I did just so you
我做 的第一件事 就是 你
know is that what do you think I did
知道的是， 你认为我做了什么
very soon feeling made through the
很快感觉通过
entire video I did that Facebook yeah
整个视频我这样做的Facebook 耶
you remember that no oh yeah that one oh
你记住， 没有哦耶那一个哦
yeah and I was actually just making up
是的，我实际上只是在弥补
that legit actually had actually
其实合法的确有其实
happened you forgot already
发生了你已经忘了
I didn't really expected her to guess
我真的没想到她 会猜测
here the chat room probably knows I
这里聊天室可能知道我
plugged the SD card into the computer I
将SD卡插入计算机 I中
copied the files over to the server
将文件复制到 服务器
I added your folder which I created on
我添加了我创建的文件夹
the server to our nightly backup and I
服务器到 我们每晚的备份和我
backed it up off-site so your is backed
支持它离开现场，所以你的支持
up immediately right because we've been
达立即正确的 ，因为我们已经
through this where you know people who
通过这个你认识 谁的人
you know do favors for friends and put
你知道做朋友的好处，并把
their camera at the wedding and film it
他们的相机在婚礼上拍摄它
and then accidentally delete it or you
然后意外删除它或你
know hard drive crashes or something
知道硬盘崩溃什么的
like that so that is ruled out so so
像 这样 被排除了那么那么
that made me think what are you doing
这让我觉得你在做什么
for your backups now that you're married
现在你已经结婚了
and honestly the first thing I thought
老实说我是第一件想到的事情
about once I got back to work cuz I've
大概有一次我回到 工作 因为我已经
been like boycotting work for like a
就像抵制工作一样
week and it was too good idea anyways
无论如何 ， 这 是一个好主意
was I honestly should start backing up
我真的 应该开始备份
my files better which right now I have a
我的文件更好， 现在我有一个
dinosaur of an external hard drive they
他们的外部硬盘的 恐龙
will actually chew through your hard
实际上会通过你的努力咀嚼
drive
驾驶
I think yeah dinosaurs are notorious for
我认为 恐龙是臭名昭着 的
that good good
那很好
but basically I've got nothing that's
但基本上我 什么都没有
all I have and then I have CDs that I'm
我的全部，然后我有我的CD
about to buy I I really need some some
即将购买II真的需要一些
awesome externals I want two of them so
真棒外部我想他们两个如此
I have one at home when elsewhere and I
我一个人在家时，其他地方我
have a plug yeah I'm kind of glad I
有一个插头耶 我很高兴我
asked because the you know because my
问， 因为你知道， 因为我的
thinking was okay I've got your videos
思维还行，我有你的视频
now I got to get them to you but if I
现在我得把它们给你，但如果我
give them to you right and then I delete
把它们给你， 然后我删除
them from my system what's gonna happen
他们从我的系统会 发生 什么 事情
to your wedding video because I don't
到你的婚礼视频，因为我没有
want to hear from you in five years and
想听到你在五年
say yeah I put it on my laptop and all
说是的，我把它放在我的笔记本电脑 和所有
these years has just been sitting on my
这些年来一直 坐在我的身上
laptop hard drive and I dropped it in a
笔记本电脑硬盘驱动器，我把它放在一个
pool totally and it's something yeah
完全池，这是一些耶
people at home that are listening and
人在家中 被倾听 和
not watching just actually they didn't
没有注意到他们实际上没有
realize that that was me talking the
意识到那是我在说 的
impression was incredible Wow
印象令人难以置信哇
good at what I do folks okay so you need
善于处理我所做的事情， 所以你需要
to well what are you moving forward yeah
要清楚什么是你前进 耶
okay well let's let's pull up you know
好吧，让我们让我们拉你知道
there's there's so many different places
那里有很多不同的地方
that we could go online we have a store
我们可以上网，我们 有一家商店
here in town called Canada computers are
在这个城镇叫 加拿大电脑
just pretty handy because they kind of
只是非常方便， 因为它们
have everything and their prices are not
拥有一切，他们的价格 不是
unreasonable usually you you can compare
通常你可以比较不合理
to what is out there but you can get on
什么是在那里，但你可以得到
to their website and just kind of do it
到他们的网站 ， 只是这样做
you know go through hard drives or
你知道通过硬盘驱动器或
whatever it I extend hard drive Oh
无论它我扩展硬盘 哦
they've got lots and because I'm sure
他们有很多，因为我确定
your budget is through the roof I'm
你的预算是通过我的屋顶
gonna actually sort highest to lowest so
会 实际排序从最高到最低
they do have a lacey drive for sixteen
他们确实有十六岁的花边驱动器
hundred bucks is that within the budget
百 美元就是在预算范围内
okay we can move down the list what do
好的， 我们可以 将 名单下移
you consider sort the other way around I
你可以考虑以另一种方式排序
did see one for $4.99 $4.99 not so sure
确实看到一个4.99美元4.99美元不是那么确定
about the reliability of that one no but
关于那个人的可靠性 没有
we'll look at that in the same but okay
我们来看看， 在相同的，但没关系
so you're plugging into your MacBook or
所以你插入你的MacBook或
Y the one that I have will be plugged in
Ÿ，我会 在被插入 的 一个
yeah tomatoknight my Mac yet and it's
耶tomatoknight我的 Mac还没有
reasonably old like it doesn't have
合理老喜欢它没有
Thunderbolt
霹雳
sb3 like a USB - yeah okay so USB - is
sb3像 一个USB  - 没错，所以USB  - 是
480 megabits a second okay so it's
每秒480兆字节，所以它是
pretty fast
相当快
way better than USB 1.1 then you've got
比USB 1.1更好， 那么你 有
USB 3 which is like five gigabits a
USB 3，就像五千兆a
second faster than an internal hard
其次比 内部硬件快
drive as far as SATA you know first gen
只要你知道第一代SATA就行
goes or you've got Thunderbolt on the
或者你的Thunderbolt在 上
max but so we'll just look at like a USB
最大，但我们只是看起来像一个USB
drive because that's really the the only
因为这 是 唯一的
option for you USB - USB 3 USB 3 drives
为您选择USB -  USB 3 USB 3驱动器
are backward compatible so get a USB 3
是向后兼容的，所以得到一个 USB 3
Drive and it's not gonna it's gonna work
驱动器 ，它不会它会工作
just fine it's just gonna be at the
很好，它只是 在 那里
speed of USB - right I'm looking they've
USB的速度- 正确的我看他们已经
got like CH a C's here they've got tons
像CH a C在这里得到了 吨
of different things with a chassis like
与 底盘 不同的 东西
an external harddrive you see how these
一个外部 硬盘你看 这些 如何
ones are only like 40 bucks you can buy
只有40美元可以买到
an internal hard drive and put it inside
内部硬盘驱动器，并把它 里面
of the chassis it's kind of cool how big
它的底盘有点 酷
did you need if you can't terabyte
你是否需要，如果你不能terabyte
terabytes these are generally kind of
这些通常都是TB级的
sorted by size because they get more
按大小排序，因为它们获得更多
expensive as you go up 500 gig 500 gig
昂贵的，你去了 500演出500演出
500 gig terabyte there's our first
我们的第一个500吉比特太字节
terabyte it's a Seagate which is good
太字节它是一个希捷，这是很好的
sigue it's gonna be better than like
sigue它会 比like更好
your Western Digital there's a Western
你的西部数字 有 西方的
Digital Drive there for about the same
数字 驱动器大致 相同
price Seagate Drive for 70 bucks as a
价格希捷驱动70美元作为一个
terabyte external hard drive so that
1TB的外置硬盘驱动器， 使
sounds pretty good USB 3 so just a
听起来不错的 USB 3，所以只是一个
standard kind of external hard drive
标准种类 的外置硬盘
specs don't really matter because it's
规格并不重要，因为它
an external right you're limited to the
你限于外部权
speed of the bus your internal hard
公交车的速度你的 内部很难
drive you think about you know is it
开车送你想想，你知道 它 是
7200 rpm is it super fast or is it 5400
7200转速是超快还是5400
rpm with an external because you're
因为你是外部的转速
limited by the speed of the bus it
受巴士 速度的限制吧
doesn't really matter see so 470 bucks
没问题，因为看到 那么 470块钱
times two you get two drives and what
两次 你得到 两个驱动器 和什么
are you gonna do with them one off-site
你会在场外与他们做一次吗？
yes yes exactly
是的， 是的
good good plan right so you could you
好好计划的权利 ，所以你可以 你
could use time machine to do like an
可以使用时间机器做一个
incremental yep on the drive that you
你的驱动器上的增量是
have at home take that one here's how
在家里拿这个那个是这样的
you would have to do it you couldn't go
你必须这样做，你不能去
get the one and bring it home to run
得到一个并带回家 运行
another backup because then all three
因为那三个都是另一个备份
drives your laptop and the two external
驱动你的笔记本电脑和两个外部
hard drives are now at one location so
硬盘驱动器现在正处于一个位置，以便
yes
是
and if there's if you have a fire you're
如果你有火的话
not apt to grab everything you gotta get
不容易抓住你 得到的一切
out right just as an example so so what
只是作为一个例子， 所以如此如此
you could do is take your one hard drive
你可以做的是把你的一个硬盘驱动器
to wherever it is that you are storing
到任何你 正在存储的地方
the other hard drive switch it and then
其它硬盘 切换， 然后
update so you never have all three
更新，所以你从来没有三个
drives in one location at once that
在一个位置驱动了一次，
could work really well this is the place
可以工作得很好 这 就是这个地方
where you putting in have internet yes
在这里你将 在有 互联网是
so you can put your Pogoplug there no
所以你可以把你的Pogoplug有 没有
nice so you actually access the drive
很好， 所以你实际上访问驱动器
remotely brilliant
遥远辉煌
sounds like a good scenario I want an
听起来像是我想要的一个好场景
update next time that you're here right
下次更新时，你在这里是 正确的
miraculously two fires have one in each
奇迹般的两场大火每场都有一场
location no that never happens
地点没有， 从来没有发生
oh good never happens it happens to be
哦，从来没有发生过，恰巧 是
in the shadow back you know and whatever
在影子后面你知道什么
so that's pretty good 60 70 bucks for
所以这是相当不错的60 70 美元
terabyte drive so check it but they're
terabyte驱动器，所以检查它，但他们
just on the south end area so you just
只是在 南端地区，所以你只是
go take a look hey welcome to everybody
去看看嘿欢迎大家
who's joining us in the chatroom nice to
谁 愿意 和我们 聊聊聊天室
see ya good to see everybody we've got
看到 你很高兴看到我们拥有的每一个人
an exciting show for you tonight and
为你今晚和晚上的精彩节目
we've got the cat phone if you want to
如果你愿意，我们有猫电话
give us a call get your questions in two
给我们打电话，让 你的问题在 两个
five four five cat five TV what else
5个 四五猫五个新电视转播还有什么
have we got
我们有没有
just giving you a chance to speak lots
只是给你一个发言的机会
of congrats Conan that's really nice
恭喜 Conan ，这真的很好
thanks everybody for her on behalf of it
感谢大家为她 代表
thank you
谢谢
I want to say thank you as well to
我想说谢谢你，以及 对
viewers who were able to send in
观众 谁能够 送入
donations this week we greatly greatly
我们这周的捐款大大增加
appreciate that very very much if you'd
对此非常非常 多 ，如果你想
like me to remote into your system and
像我一样远程进入你的系统和
perform any kind of service tonight to
执行任何种类 今晚服务， 以
help you repair something we can do that
帮助您修复的东西 ，我们可以做到这一点
live on the air using TeamViewer so just
只需使用TeamViewer即可直播
install TeamViewer and then just private
安装TeamViewer ，然后只是私人
message me in the chatroom
在 聊天室给我发消息
its category five on freenode all right
它 在freenode上的第五 类是 好的
well hey it have you ever been ok you go
嘿，你有没有好，你走了
out your wedding is a perfect example
你的婚礼是一个完美的 例子
why don't I just start over because it
为什么我不重新开始，因为它
makes editing so much easier so Christa
让Christa更容易编辑
your wedding just happened you've got
你的婚礼恰好发生了
all these photos right and they're
所有这些照片的权利，他们是
massively
大规模
has everybody you write probably invited
有你写的每个人都可能邀请
your friends with the best cameras
你的朋友用最好的相机
because they've got the best cameras and
因为他们有最好的相机和
they're huge that's why we exactly yeah
他们是巨大的，这就是为什么我们究竟 是啊
people with good cameras they just how
拥有好相机的人他们只是如何
they made the less hey hey Doug you've
他们做了少 嘿道格你已经
got a good camera right sounds like I
有一个很好的相机 就像我一样
know it's amazing to come to a wedding
知道参加婚礼是很棒的
so you could oh no but you get this like
所以你可以 哦，但你得到这个样子
incredible amount of photos and they're
令人难以置信的数量 的照片，他们是
huge days because they're digital and
巨大的日子， 因为他们是数字化的
they're they're massive you want to
他们是你想要的巨大
email them to mom and dad you want to
通过电子邮件发送给您想要的妈妈和爸爸
get them around and I don't know about
让他们在身边 ，我不知道
you but I have friends and family who
你但我有 朋友和 家人 谁
adamantly refuse to use Facebook so sure
坚决拒绝使用Facebook如此肯定
I put my photos up on Facebook and it
我把我的照片了 Facebook和 它
does some scaling and everything but
做一些缩放和一切， 但
there are other people that you need to
还有其他人需要你
email the photos to seem so old-school
发送照片看起来很老派
emailing your photos what just just
通过电子邮件发送您的照片
friend me on Facebook man but seriously
朋友，我在Facebook上的人，但 认真
so you encounter that and what do you do
所以你遇到这种情况，你做了什么
with these great big files that are you
与这些伟大的大文件是你
know 6 7 8 10 Meg's each and you've got
知道6 7 8 10梅格的 每一个，你有
20 of them well you MOG Rifai them what
他们中的 20个好你 MOG Rifai他们 什么
it's like modified with a ger legit word
它就像修改了合法的单词一样
like I just made it up just right like
就像我刚才提出 它 恰到好处像
that but it's very convenient that it
这一点，但它是非常方便的 ，它
actually is a real thing so gonna show
实际上是一件真实的事情， 所以会显示
you how to do this if this is if this is
如果是这样的话，你该如何做到这一点
you then here you go I'm gonna grab a
你然后 在这里你走我要去抢一个
handful of pictures from last week's
来自上周的一些照片
shows gallery there we go perfect
显示那里我们去完美的画廊
examples just because they're big photos
仅仅因为他们是大照片的例子
see how long this one takes to load
看看这个加载需要多长时间
there it is so if I actually like zoom
如果我真的喜欢缩放 ，那就是这样
into full its it's a pretty big photo
充分 它是一张相当大的照片
right there you go so we want to send
就在那里你去，所以我们 想发送
this photo to family and friends let's
这张照片给家人和朋友
grab all these photos okay first thing
抓住所有这些照片好 第一件事
you want to do when you're MOG Rifai
当你是MOG Rifai时你想要做
anytime you're doing any image
任何时候你都在做任何形象
manipulation and what do you do krista
操纵， 你做什么 克里斯塔
when you're you save the original files
当你保存 原始文件时
yes high-five
是高五
she got a backup question right you have
她有一个正确的备份问题
a backup
备份
you never overwrite your original I call
你永远不会覆盖你原来的电话
them the master file right sweet well
他们的主文件很好
done okay so I am I'm very proud okay so
做得好，所以我很自豪，所以我很自豪
now I'm copying the original files so
现在我正在复制原始文件
that I never
我 从来没有
at them because I don't want to
因为我不想
overwrite my originals I'm gonna go to
覆盖我的 原件 我要去
my desktop create a new folder we're
我的桌面上创建了一个新的文件夹
gonna just call this pictures go in
要把这张照片叫进去
there paste those now I have a copy
有粘贴现在我有一个副本
they're huge there they are
他们在那里是巨大的
take a moment to load because they're
花点时间加载， 因为他们是
quite big that okay so these are just
这很好，所以这些都是
from the photo gallery from category 5
来自类别5 的照片库
TV for episode number 309 that's what
第309集的电视，这是什么
these photos are just so that I have
这些照片只是让我拥有
something to use as an example I'm going
作为 我要去的 一个例子
to go into my terminal because these are
进入我的终端， 因为这些
much too big to email to mom and dad
太大而无法发送给妈妈和 爸爸
sudo apt-get install image magic and
sudo apt-get install image魔术和
magic has a K that's all one word what
魔术有一个 K这就是 所有的一个词
do you want to do do you want to go for
你想做什么，你 想要 去
it yes this particular step installing
它是这个特定的步骤安装
image magic is only needed once once
图像魔术只需要一次
you've installed it you've got it on
你已经安装了它，你已经得到了它
your computer you never have to do this
你的 电脑 你永远不必这样做
step again but then you'll be able to do
再来一次， 但你 可以做到
what we're about to show you
我们即将展示给你
there we go it's going through
我们走它会通过
installing setting up image magic on
安装设置图像魔术
Linux and it's done so I'm gonna go into
Linux已经完成，所以 我 要 进入
CD desktop pictures now you see there's
现在你看到的CD桌面图片
all my pictures and you'll see that they
我的所有照片，你会看到 他们
are quite large and the three Meg range
是相当大 的 三Meg范围
there's one there that's five and a
有一个是五个 和一个
quarter Meg definitely not gonna be able
季梅格绝对不会能够
to send this folder so what I can do is
发送这个文件夹，所以我 能做的是
I can now type ma graph I and I have
我现在可以键入 我和我的图
that command now because I've installed
该命令现在因为我已经安装
image magic ma graph I - resize and then
图像魔术马图我 - 调整大小，然后
pick for us a format a size that is
为我们挑选一种尺寸的格式
reasonable for email let's say 640 by
合理的电子邮件让我们说640通过
480 those are going to be your maximum
这些将会是你的最大值
it's not going to stretch it's going to
它不会延伸它将会
simply maximize those that's as big as
只需最大限度地扩大那些与之相当
its going to be I'm gonna say star
它将成为我要说的明星
because it's gonna grab all of the
因为它会抓住所有 的
images or I could also say start out jpg
图像或我也可以说开始JPG
but then if I have a jpg upper case then
但如果我有一个JPG 大写的话
it's not gonna get it
它不会得到它
so we'll just do star and hit enter and
所以我们只是做明星，然后按Enter键
you'll see what happens now is that each
你会看到现在 发生的是 每一个
photo is just gonna disappear for just a
照片只是要去消失 只是一个
moment because it's rewriting each one
那一刻 ，因为它重写每一个
of those photos and now if I click on
这些照片的，现在如果我点击
that file it's already done that's as
那个文件已经 完成了
quick as it is that's the quickest tip
快， 因为 这是 最快捷的提示
ever double click on that file look at
双击该文件看看
that click click click wait faster way
点击点击 等待更快的 方式
faster and you'll notice that the photos
更快，你会注意到照片
are now
现在
that one's six forty by four eleven it's
一个人的 六点四四十一点 才 举行 的
proportional so it maximized to 640
成比例，所以它最大化到640
pixels wide but did not stretch to 480
像素宽但不能伸展到480
however I've got one here of Hillary
然而我在 希拉里 有一个这里
that is vertical photo instead of
这是垂直的照片，而不是
horizontal and you'll notice that it
水平，你会发现 它
maximized to a height of 480 pixels and
最大化到 480像素的高度
447 pixels width so that is a fantastic
447像素的宽度，这是一个梦幻般的
tool for being able to send these photos
工具， 能够发送这些照片
to your family and friends now that
你的家人和朋友， 现在
entire folder is only one point eight
整个文件夹只有 一点八
megabytes Wow with all those photos so
兆字节哇与所有这些照片如此
MOG Rifai and it's a part of image magic
MOG Rifai ，它是图像魔法的一部分
with a K cool
与 K酷
this is category five technology TV
这是 五级技术电视
thanks for joining us tonight our
感谢今晚我们加入我们的行列
website is triple W category five dot TV
网站是三W类五点电视
I'm Robbie Ferguson I'm Krista walls
我是罗比弗格森我是克里斯塔墙
well shall we jump right into it oh is
好吧，我们应该跳 进去 哦
this that age-old question yeah the
这是 一个古老的问题耶
age-old what could the question be you
古老的问题可能是你的问题
forget already no I know what it is I
忘记已经不，我知道我是什么
just I think they can't respond well I
只是我认为他们不能很好地回应 我
know I can't be brilliant at everything
知道我 在任何事情上都 不会很 出色
well yeah well back up a little bit but
好吧，以及 一点点支持
remember when you came and and we did
记得当你来和我们一起时
the hacker episode we call it the hacker
黑客事件我们称之为黑客
episode where we kind of dressed a
我们穿着一件衣服的情节
little goofy and we dimmed the lights
一点点高兴，我们昏暗的灯光
and made everything green and and one of
并把所有东西都变成绿色和和其中之一
the things that I did is I made my
我做的事情是我做了我的
computer look kind of cool by installing
电脑通过安装看起来很酷
some desktop widgets and since then I
一些桌面小部件，从那时起我
would liked them so I just left them
会喜欢他们，所以 我只是离开他们
there and I get a fair number of email
在那里，我收到了相当 数量的电子邮件
people saying oh how do I get that what
人们说哦，我怎么知道那是什么
is that conky can I have that - all
我可以拥有这个 - 所有的
cocky and I can't get it so tonight
自大，我今晚得不到它
we're gonna actually show you how to
我们会告诉你如何
obtain those kinds of things on your
在你的身上获得这些东西
desktop if you're running Linux this is
桌面如果你正在运行Linux这是
for you if you're running Windows or Mac
为你如果 你正在运行 Windows或Mac
you can switch there is hope for you yet
您可以切换是有希望 的 ，你还
all these things are free and you saw
所有这些东西都是免费的， 你看到了
you saw how easy it is to install things
你看到安装东西是 多么容易
on Linux it's a simple quick command or
在Linux上它是一个简单的快速命令或
you can use a package manager and it's
你 可以使用包管理器
easy easy breezy so a couple of things
轻松轻松愉快，所以几件事情
that we need to start out with of course
我们 当然 需要 开始
we want to install things that are not
我们想要安装不是的东西
just a track
只是一条轨道
and cool-looking but stuff that's useful
和冷静看， 但有用的东西
great so we want to know okay is our
太好了，所以我们想知道好的是我们的
hard drive almost out of space is our
硬盘几乎 空间 不足 是我们的
CPU sitting at 100% or is it sitting
CPU坐在100％或坐着
floating around 31 oh those kinds of
漂浮在31喔那些 种类
things what's our network traffic things
事情是什么，我们的网络交通 事情
like here's one is my cpu overheating
像这里有一个是我的 CPU过热
right hmm do you know whether your CPU
嗯，你知道你的CPU吗
is too hot I don't how would you know
太热了我不 知道你怎么知道
I'll be right using things like this
我马上就使用 这样 的事情
again it becomes something that's not
它再次成为 不是
just attractive and cool-looking but
只是有吸引力和冷静看， 但
also something that's useful because you
也是因为你有用的东西
can now access that kind of information
现在可以访问 这种 信息
so speaking of being able to monitor
所以说能够监控
temperatures the first thing that we
温度是我们的第一件事情
need to do is install something called
需要做的是安装 所谓的东西
LM sensors so we're gonna go sudo
LM传感器，所以我们要去sudo
apt-get update that's going to load your
apt-get update将会加载你的
package list brand new and fresh and
包列表全新的， 清新
then we're gonna go sudo apt-get install
那么我们会去sudo apt-get install
is the command notice I'm doing this
是我正在执行此操作的命令 通知
from the terminal because I want you to
从终端 ，因为我要你
feel comfortable there it's not as it's
在那里感觉舒适，它不是那样
not a scary place sudo means become
不是一个可怕的地方sudo意味着成为
super user it's super user do is what
超级用户是超级用户做的是什么
you're doing sudo allows you to have
你在做 sudo让你拥有
administrator access to your computer
管理员访问您的计算机
this is one of the reasons Linux is a
这是Linux的原因之一
lot more safe and you don't get viruses
更安全，你不会感染 病毒
is because you're not typically running
是因为你通常不会跑步
as an administrator so sudo apt-get is
作为管理员， 所以sudo apt-get是
this program that we're gonna use in
这个程序，我们 在 要去使用
order to install this program the
为了安装这个程序
command we're gonna use is install and
我们要使用的命令是install和
the program that we're going to use is
我们要使用的程序是
called LM - send Soares hit enter you'll
叫LM - 发送Soares打进你会
see that in my system it says LM sensors
在我的系统中看到它说LM传感器
is already the newest version reason for
已经是最新版本的原因
that Christa is because this requires a
克里斯塔是因为这需要一个
reboot and I knew that so I just quickly
重启，我知道，所以我很快
installed this before the show I still
在演出之前我仍然安装了这个
wanted to demonstrate how it's done
想演示 它是如何完成的
because I know that you at home you're
因为我知道 你在家里是你的
probably not going to already have that
可能不会 有 这个
configured and set up so next step now
配置和现在 建立因此下一 步骤
that we've done that is we're gonna type
我们已经完成了，我们要打字
sudo you remember what that does it
sudo 你还记得 那是什么
turns us into an administrator so that
把我们变成一个管理员，以便
we make changes to our computer and
我们对我们的 计算机 进行了更改
we're gonna type send sores
我们会输入发送 疮
- detect and what that command is going
- 检测以及该命令正在执行的内容
to do is it's going to detect all of the
要做的是它会检测所有的
available sense
可用的感觉
that are a part of your particular
这是你特定的一部分
configuration usually safe just to go
配置通常只是安全去
with the defaults so see if I hit enter
与默认值，所以看看我是否 输入
it's going to say yes it will check my
它会说是的，它会检查我的
CPU memory controllers for sensors so
用于传感器的 CPU存储器控制器
let it go it says that it found one a
让它去吧它说它 找到了一个
digital thermal sensor on my Intel chip
数字热传感器在我的英特尔芯片上
cool all right so now next one is super
很酷 所以现在下 一个超级
i/o chips contain embedded sensors do
I / O芯片包含嵌入的传感器 做
you want to scan for those default is
你想扫描那些默认的是
yes so I'm gonna let it do it I'm gonna
是的，所以我会让它做它我会去的
hit enter next one you know keeps going
点击进入下 一个 你知道继续
and going I don't need to read each one
并且我不需要阅读每一个
you can read them if you want but here's
你可以阅读他们，如果你想，但在这里
one that says that's probably to say no
一个说 这可能会说不
so I'm just gonna again go with the
所以我只是要再次和我一起去
defaults unless I know that I want to
默认除非我知道，我想
say yes yes yes yes
说是的是的是的
checking my Nvidia chipset scanning for
检查我的Nvidia芯片组扫描
all the stuff there we go let's picked
我们去的所有东西都是我们 选择的
up one sensor there on my own video chip
在我自己的视频芯片上安装一个传感器
enter now follow a summary of the probes
现在输入下面的探针摘要
here we go okay so it's found a couple
这里我们走了， 所以发现了一对夫妇
of different ones that it could add to
它可以增加 的不同的那些
our kernel in order to allow our widgets
我们的内核为了让我们的小部件
to be able to monitor the thermal
能够监测热量
sensors so do you want to automatically
传感器，所以你想自动
add that to ease TC modules here's the
补充说，这是为了缓解TC模块的问题
one place where you're going to say the
一个你会说的地方
opposite of what it is defaulting to
它默认 到相对的
you're gonna say most likely yes make a
你会说最有可能的是 让一个
note of /et see modules and the two
注意/ et参见模块和二者
lines that are being added the reason
正在增加的原因线
that you want to make a note of that is
你想记下的 是
because if you have trouble booting your
因为如果你无法启动你的
computer now after this change for some
现在这台计算机改变了一些
strange reason you can now use a boot CD
奇怪的原因， 你现在可以使用启动 光盘
like a live CD edit the et Cie slash
就像一张Live CD编辑et Cie斜线一样
modules and comment out those two lines
模块并注释掉这两行
until you figure it out so just make a
直到你看着办吧所以 只是做一个
mental note write it down on a little
心理记录 稍微 写下来
piece of scrap paper until you've
废纸 一张 ，直到你
rebooted a couple times just to know
重新启动了几次才知道
that everything is gonna be safe so once
一切都会安全一次
you've said yes to that question I'm
你对我的这个问题表示肯定
gonna say no because I've already done
会说不， 因为我已经完成了
it
它
it will have already done all that stuff
它已经做了所有 的 东西
and then you're going to reboot your
然后你会重新启动 你的
computer normally or you can just do
电脑正常或你可以做
sudo reboot just like that I don't want
sudo 重启就像 我不想要的那样
to do that because that's what we're
这样做是因为我们就是这样
avoiding
避免
so now that I've got LM sensors
所以现在我有了LM传感器
installed I can monitor my CPU
安装我 可以监视我的CPU
temperature and those kinds of things
温度和这些 东西
kind of cool so let's let's get conky
有点酷，让我们来看看吧
installed first and foremost conky I
安装首先和最重要的我
would say you know I I have to show it
会说你知道我必须展示它
because it is you know we almost have to
因为你知道我们几乎不得不这样做
pay homage to conky being as awesome as
祭奠Conky的 是作为作为真棒
it is but it is a little bit more tricky
这是但它有点棘手
to get familiar with and to learn your
熟悉 并学习 你的
way around because it's a bit of a
办法解决 ，因为它是一个有点
scripting language in in some regards so
脚本语言在某些方面如此
you actually have to create your own
你实际上必须创造你 自己的
sensors or find examples online that you
传感器或在网上找到你的例子
can that people have shared online so so
那么 人们可以在线分享
it's a bit more you know it's a little
它有点多，你知道它有点儿
more hacker esque if you will it's a
如果你愿意的话，更多的黑客服饰
very it's it's very well used in the
非常适合 在这里使用
crunchbang Linux community which has
crunchbang Linux社区有哪些
that kind of hacker ish feel to it as
那种黑客感觉到 它
far as the operating system goes I love
就像 我喜欢 的操作系统一样
it you saw review a long time ago on on
你很久以前就看过评论
category 5 TV of crunchbang so we'll
crunchbang第5类电视，所以我们会
just quickly take a look at it not too
只是快速 看看它不太
much in depth because it is something
很深入，因为 它是一些东西
that you're gonna need to get into the
你 需要进入
scripting end of things in order to
脚本结尾的事情，以便
really get good at sudo apt-get install
真的很擅长sudo apt-get install
conky just like it sounds Co and Kay why
conky就像它听起来 Co和Kay一样
and here we go it's just gonna download
在这里，我们去它只是要下载
see this is how Linux installs things
看到这是Linux如何安装的东西
you don't need to go buy a CDE or
你不需要去购买 CDE或者
anything you just get it online so there
任何你只是在网上获得的东西
we go so now I can't actually do
我们现在走了，现在我实际上做不到了
anything with conky because I haven't
因为我没有，所以有点混乱
got anything set up as far as widgets go
只要小部件已经安装就可以设置任何东西
there's no GUI there's no you know thing
没有GUI，没有你知道的事情
that I can bring up and just start
我可以提出 并开始
dragging and dropping widgets onto my
拖放小部件到我的
desktop that's not how conky works but
桌面这不是多么conky工作，但
what we do have like I said crunchbang
我们所做的就像我说crunchbang
is is one of the communities that uses
是使用的社区之一
it fairly heavily so I've taken a look
它相当重，所以我 看了一下
at their forum and there are a few great
在他们的论坛上，有几个 伟大的
posts there I'm gonna go to cap 5 dot TV
帖子还有我要去封顶 5点电视
slash conky and that's actually going to
削减 的Conky而这实际上是 要
redirect you to the crunchbang forums
将你重定向到crunchbang论坛
and you'll see that here some wonderful
你会在这里看到一些美妙的
view users of that distribution such as
查看该分配的用户， 如
wanderer here in one of the first posts
流浪者在这里的第一个职位之一
or in the first post has posted the
或者在第一篇文章中已经发布了
script for their configuration for conky
脚本为他们的conky配置
and it looks really complex doesn't
它看起来非常复杂不
here's another one oh hey here's root
这里的另一个 嘿这里的 根
says hey I like what you did here's what
说，嘿，我喜欢你在这里做的是什么
I did and it looks pretty overwhelming
我做了，看起来非常惊人
and as a novice user I might say well
作为新手用户，我可能会说得很好
that's crazy amounts of work but it's
这是疯狂的工作量，但它是
not because they're helpful here I'm
不是因为他们对我有帮助
gonna show you what you do it's really
要告诉你你做了什么
not that complicated what you would do
没有那么复杂，你会做什么
is well first of all I'll show you what
首先我会告诉 你什么
we can't do yet
我们还不能做
I'm gonna run conky I'm gonna minimize
我要运行conky我会尽量减少
everything I'm gonna just type in conky
我 只需输入conky即可
well and you'll see I do have a
好吧，你会看到我有 一个
configuration file all right I need to
配置文件中 的所有 的权利 ， 我需要
clear out the configuration I was doing
清除我正在做 的 配置
some testing before but what we'll do
一些测试之前，但我们会做什么
all right
好吧
if you haven't run conky before and
如果你之前还没有运行过conky
haven't set up any scripts it's going to
没有设置任何脚本
actually just it might just crash out it
实际上只是它可能会让它崩溃
might do nothing it might give you some
可能无所作为，它可能会给你一些
kind of you know a little bit of
有点你知道 的
gibberish like I had there but what you
像我在那里但你是什么样的胡言乱语
can do with these configurations is now
现在可以用这些配置来做
I can just simply copy any of this text
我可以简单地复制这些文字
so or the whole script see what I'm
所以或整个脚本看看我是什么
gonna do is just highlight this script
要做的只是突出 这个剧本
here copy that to my clipboard and in my
这里复制到我的剪贴板和我的
home folder I'm gonna create a new file
家庭文件夹我要创建一个新 文件
and we're gonna call it dot cuz it's a
我们会打电话给 它， 因为它是一个
hidden file conky Farsi just like that
隐藏的文件 conky波斯就是这样
and then hit enter and you'll see that
然后按回车，你会看到
I've already got one there that's why it
我已经有一个 这就是它的原因
was showing something up let's see if I
显示了一些东西，让我们看看我是否
can you know what I'm just gonna delete
你能知道我刚才要删除的内容吗？
the original one and then I can do this
原来的，然后我可以做到这一点
correctly
正确地
conky RC there it is
conky RC在那里
I can backtrack just a little bit there
我可以在那里稍微回溯一下
we go beautiful Thanks all right so what
我们去 美丽 感谢所有 正确的如此
I can't do with conky here if I run it
如果我运行它，我无法在这里使用conky
okay so it's giving me some kind of a
好吧，所以它 给了 我 一些
default here and it's but there's no
默认在这里，但它没有
there's no configuration and it's just
没有配置，只是
running the default kind of settings
运行默认的设置
using the scripts that are here on this
使用在这里对 这个脚本
forum post just as an example I can copy
论坛帖子只是作为一个 例子， 我可以复制
what other people have accomplished with
其他人完成了什么
conky
Conky的
highlight copy and now go into my home
突出副本，现在进入我的家
folder make a new file and I'm gonna
文件夹创建一个新文件，我 会去的
call it dot conky R see that's the conky
称它为点conky R看到这是conky
configuration file and open that file in
配置文件并打开该文件
your favorite text editor I'm using
您 正在 使用的 最喜欢的文本编辑器
pluma it might be G at it and simply
pluma 它可能是G而且简单
paste in what you copied from the the
粘贴你从中复制 的内容
forum there at cat5 TV slash conky and
论坛里面的 五类电视斜线Conky的 和
now I can close everything and now when
现在我可以关闭一切，现在当
I run conky with the simple command
我用简单的命令运行conky
conky and I can add that to my startup
conky，我可以添加到 我的启动
applications you'll see the okay now
应用程序， 你会看到现在好了
things have changed it's actually using
事情已经改变了它的实际使用
someone else's cool configuration that
别人的酷配置
they've made and it's added this nice
他们已经做出来了，并且增加了这一点
panel on the right-hand side you'll see
你会看到右侧的面板
the conky is a little bit more text
conky是一点点文字
driven than what I would go with because
比我会 去的要多，因为
we're not going for you know the little
我们不会为你 知道这个小小的
tiny text it's it's very very functional
小文本它是非常非常实用的
very very useful there's only one houl
非常非常有用的只有一个口袋
well yeah we kind of want that Flair
好吧，我们有点想要 Flair
factor of your graphic designer so you
你的图形设计师的因素， 所以你
probably want like the you know the 3d
可能想要像你所 知道的3d
yeah a little bit nicer than just plain
是一点点 比简单的 更好
text and text ASCII kind of bar graphs
文本 和文本ASCII种类的条形图
kind of thing so that's kind of just
这种事情就是这样
coffee at a at a real quick glance I'm
咖啡 在一个真正的快速浏览我
gonna kill it by kill all - 9 conky and
要杀死所有 - 9 conky和
it's off my screen now next up in our
现在 我们的屏幕已经关闭了
tutorial this is the one that we
教程，这是 一个我们
actually used on the show Krista and I
实际上在节目Krista 和我上使用
for our hacker episode and you've seen
对于我们的黑客插曲，你已经看到了
it on my screen ever since then I'm
从那时起我就一直在我的屏幕上
gonna go sudo apt-get install screen
要去sudo apt-get安装屏幕
lets the application is called screen
让应用程序被称为 屏幕
let's and do we want to install yep
让我们来做我们想要安装的产品
just check that it's not going to remove
只是检查它不会删除
anything that's critical and so it goes
任何关键的事情都会发生
through the internet and finds all the
通过互联网，找到所有的
files that it needs in order to install
它需要安装的文件
this particular widget daemon there we
这个特定的小部件守护进程在那里我们
go
走
almost there and it's done wow that was
几乎在那里， 这是完成哇
pretty quick it is it is ok so this one
相当快是它是 确定所以这一块
I can run it from the terminal if I want
如果我想，我可以从终端运行它
but in fact I've got a helpful little
但实际上我 有一点帮助
tool installed on my accessories menu
工具安装在我的配件菜单上
now and I can click on that and you'll
现在，我可以点击，你会的
see that this one comes
看到这一个来
with all these great cool funky little
与所有这些伟大的酷时髦小
things so for example if I want a
例如，如果我想要一个东西
calendar I can click on clear calendar
日历我可以点击清除日历
and I can click over here this is how
我可以点击 这里， 这是如何
this one works you highlight the one
这一个作品你突出了 一个
that you want and then go start/stop so
你想要的， 然后 去开始/停止
when I click that you'll see boom
当我点击它时，你会看到繁荣
there's a calendar and I can drag it
有一个日历，我可以 拖动 它
around my screen and you'll see that
在我的屏幕周围 ，你会看到
it's on top of my screen so let's say I
它在 我的屏幕 上方 ， 所以我们说我
want my calendar to be up there so once
希望我的日历能够在那里上过一次
I've got it where I want it
我已经把它放在了我想要的地方
now I'm gonna right-click on it and go
现在我要右击它并 去
well I can go window and I'm gonna set
好吧，我可以去窗口，我要去设置
three things I'm gonna go widget so that
三件事我要去小部件，以便
it now is something that can't be moved
它现在是不能移动的东西
well it isn't locked but it's it's a
以及它没有锁定，但它是一个
widget now it's not an application
小部件现在 它不是一个应用程序
that's running on top of everything
这是在一切运行
right click again and go window sticky
再次右键点击并粘贴窗口
so that it will kind of lock itself to
所以它会锁定自己
the to the desktop and then window lock
到桌面，然后窗口锁定
that's the final one and of course there
这是最后一个，当然那里
happens to be keep above is checked I'm
恰好是保持上面被检查我
gonna actually change that to keep below
实际上会改变，以保持在下面
because we want it under everything so
因为我们希望在一切 如此
now I can't move it when I click if I
现在当我点击时，我无法移动它
move stuff around it goes over top of it
移动的东西围绕它越过 它的 顶部
and it's a part of my desktop I can
这 是我的桌面 的一部分
right click on it I can stylize it a
用鼠标右键点击 它我可以设置它的风格
little bit I can go theme and I can go
一点点我可以去主题，我可以去
no background and now it's just a part
没有背景，现在它 只是一个部分
of my desktop and it looks pretty cool
我的桌面 ，它看起来很酷
as far as the calendar goes it's
就日历而言
interactive so I can actually change the
互动，所以我 实际上 可以 改变
month and year and all that kind of
月，年和所有这一类
stuff okay so next up you know if you're
东西好，所以接下来你知道，如果你是
on a laptop you can add battery
在笔记本电脑上， 您可以添加电池
monitoring for example I have no battery
监控例如我没有电池
so that's what it tells me that's so
所以这就是它告诉我的
helpful yep just in case I didn't know
以防万一我不知道，这很有帮助
you know all these handy little things I
你知道我所有这些方便的小东西
don't need to go through because you're
不需要 ，因为你 要经过
gonna want to click through and check
想要点击并检查
out some of the widgets that are there
去掉 那里的一些小部件
for you but the one that everybody you
对你而言，那是你所有人
know comes and emails me about and says
知道来了，并​​发邮件给我说，并说
how did you do that is the what do they
你怎么做 那是他们做的
call it here it's called the ring sensor
在这里称之为 环形传感器
so with ring sensors we're able to
所以我们可以用环形传感器
create this really really cool effect
创造这真的非常酷的效果
I'm gonna show you how to do this so
我会 告诉你如何 做到这一点
highlight ring sensors here and now
在这里和现在强调环形传感器
we're gonna start it and you'll see that
我们要开始它，你会看到
it's just throwing a CPU monitor up at
它只是扔CPU监视器
the top there which I can drag around
顶部有，我可以左右拖动
so I'm gonna bring it over here and drop
所以我会把它带到 这里 然后放下
it onto my desktop and I'm gonna
它到我的桌面上，我会去的
right-click on it and I can do those
右键点击它 ，我可以做到这一点
same things window widget window sticky
同样的东西 窗口小部件窗口粘滞
window lock window keep below so now
窗口锁定窗口现在保持在如下
it's part of my desktop can't be moved
它是我的桌面无法移动的一部分
doesn't appear to be you know
似乎并不知道
interactive in any way it's just part of
以任何方式交互它只是其中的一部分
the death and the desktop now I'm gonna
死亡和 桌面现在我 要去
right click on it again and I can change
再次 右键点击 它 ，我可以改变
things like the size which I'll show you
像我会告诉你的尺寸
in a few moments and go properties and
在一瞬间，去财产和
make changes to what sensor it's using
改变它使用的传感器
so right now it's showing me my first
所以现在它向我展示了我的第一个
CPU core you might that want this to be
你可能 想要这样做的CPU 核心
Ram so now it's showing me my RAM for
拉姆 所以现在它显示了我 的 RAM
example so you can change all those
例如，您可以更改所有这些
kinds of settings so let's leave that
让我们 离开 那种设置
one at Ram and now I'm going to in fact
一个在 拉姆，现在我 要去实际上
click over here and go launch slash ad
点击这里，然后启动斜杠 广告
making sure that ring sensors is still
确保环形传感器仍然存在
selected so when I click that it's going
选择，所以当我点击它的 时候
to add a second ring selector on to my
在我的电脑上添加第二个选择器
screen there you go so now I've got
现在，我已经拥有了屏幕
access to that so now I can move this
访问 该所以现在我可以将这个
one over and you'll notice that they
一个结束， 你会注意到他们
look exactly the same I don't want that
看起来完全 一样 我不想那样
I want them to be different so I'm gonna
我希望他们 有所 不同，所以 我会
right click and go window
点击右键，然后转到窗口
let's leave window for now let's go size
现在让我们离开窗口，让我们去体积
and we're gonna change this one to 60%
我们会把这个改成 60％
so it's a little bit smaller and put it
所以它是一个小一点，并把它
wherever we want and say okay well
无论我们想要什么，并 说 好
that's what it looks like okay now let's
这就是现在看起来没问题吧
make it a little bit bigger than that
让它比这更大一点
we'll go size and we'll go 80% and we're
我们会 扩大规模，我们会去 80％，我们会
gonna drop it right there right click
要把它放在那里右键点击
and go properties options sensors and
并去属性选项传感器和
change your sensor to you know whatever
改变你的传感器， 你知道什么
you want CPU temperature we think that's
你想CPU温度，我们认为这是
pretty cool because we've installed our
很酷，因为我们已经安装了我们的
LM sensors now and if it works see if it
LM传感器现在，如果它工作，看看它
goes there we go sixty degrees doesn't
去那里我们去 六十 度 不
really work in that particular size and
真的 在这个特定的 大小和工作
we might have trouble with that one just
我们可能 有 一个 麻烦 正好
because of the way that it's laying out
因为 它铺设的方式
the text so it's not perfect and in any
该文本，所以它不完美，在任何
stretch but cool nonetheless I'm sure
尽管如此，但我很确定
that we can make some changes to it if
我们可以做，如果 一些更改，
we had a bit more time and wanted to
我们有更多的时间和想要
play around with it but for now you know
玩 它，但 现在你知道
I'll pick one that works really really
我会选择一个真正有效的工具
well you can see even I can even see the
你 甚至 可以看到 我甚至可以看到
temperature of my GPU so that was the
我的GPU的温度是这样的
CPU
中央处理器
just changed a GPU core and I'll be able
只是改变了一个GPU核心 ，我就可以
to see that as well there it is see that
看到 这一点，它也看到了
looks a little better NVIDIA GPU okay so
看起来好一点的 NVIDIA GPU 可以
I can right-click on that let's pretend
我可以右键点击，让我们假装
that that's what we want
那就是我们想要的
properties options sensors and let's
属性选项传感器和让我们来
change the front color of this
改变这个的前面颜色
particular sensor to be you know let's
特定的传感器，你知道让我们来
say red and the text color we'll leave
说红色和 我们将离开的文字颜色
it as white ring thickness make it a bit
它作为白色的戒指厚度使它有点
thicker just so that there's some
更厚，以至于有一些
differentiation between the different
区别 不同
sensors let's see how that goes and we
传感器让我们看看如何和我们
can also a game as we're waiting there
也可在游戏中，我们正在等候在 那里
it goes I can add another one and so I'm
它可以添加另一个，所以我是
putting these all over the desktop and I
把这些放在桌面和 我身上
can set them to be whatever I want them
可以将它们设置为我想要的任何东西
to be here's another one and let's you
在这里是 另一个，让你
know we can leave this one at CPU
知道我们可以把这个留给 CPU
because we don't have a CPU one yet but
因为我们还没有 一个CPU
let's change the front color to green
让我们改变前面的颜色为绿色
and change the ring thickness to pretty
并将环的厚度改为美观
thick
厚
let's do 40 there we go and now we've
让我们在那里做40， 现在 我们去了
got this cool thing so now we're gonna
得到这个很酷的 东西，所以 现在我们会
lock these ones to the to the desk
将这些锁在桌子上
desktop as well widget window or like
桌面 以及小部件 窗口或类似
right click on the widget window log and
右键单击小部件窗口日志和
send it to the back and we'll do the
把它发送回去，我们会做
same thing for this one over here makes
这个 在 这里的 同样的东西 使
me look like I'm using a lot of CPU to
我看起来像我使用 了很多CPU
do this eh don't worry yeah your system
做这个呃不要担心你的系统
won't do that that's because of our
不会这样做 是因为我们的
desktop Broadcasting System
桌面广播系统
we're actually streaming this desktop
我们实际上是在流式传输这个 桌面
over the network to Wirecast it's just
通过 网络到Wirecast它只是
really cool to be able to do that so
很酷的是 能够做到这一点，以便
there you go and there's all these other
你去了，还有其他所有
widgets that you can play with I suggest
我建议 你 可以玩的小工具
that you give it a go you know check out
你给它一个去你知道退房
some of the meters that are there being
一些米的 存在
able to you know put these things
能够让你知道把这些东西
anywhere move them around your desktop
随时随地将它们移动到桌面上
and then lock them and then of course
然后锁定他们 ，然后当然
with ring switcher you know highlight
与你知道的环形切换器突出显示
that and say I want to auto start this
并说我想自动启动这个
on login and calendar we added that one
在登录和日历中我们添加了一个
as well so let's also auto start that
以及让我们也 自动启动
one and now when we first boot up our
一个，现在当我们第一次 启动我们的
computer it's going to look something
电脑它会看起来像什么
like that
像那样
so we've got these really cool widgets
所以我们有这些非常酷的小部件
that are now a part of my desktop I
现在是 我的桌面I 的一部分
can't drag them I can't accidentally
不能拖他们我不能不小心
move them they're not highlight able or
移动他们，他们不突出能够或
anything they are literally a nice
他们从字面上来说都是很好的
little portion of my desk nice it's a
我的桌子的一小部分很好，它是一个
good feature to not be able to
良好的功能，不能够
accidentally select them and it would
意外地选择它们，它会
happen it would absolutely happen so
发生它 绝对会发生如此
very cool stuff so check out our website
非常酷的东西，所以看看我们的网站
category 5 TV and if you have any
5 类 电视，如果你有任何
questions for us
问题给我们
or if there's anything that you want to
或者如果有任何你想要 的
learn just pop us an email live at
学习只需在我们的电子邮件中直播
category-five TV there you have it all
五类电视，你有 这 一切
right you ready Oh am i ready time for
就在 你 准备哦， 是 我 的 准备 时间
the top stories from the category 5 duct
来自5类风管的最新故事
newsroom buildup ok so a soft toy
新闻编辑室确定如此 柔软的玩具
controlled by Raspberry Pi a Raspberry
由树莓派控制覆盆子
Pi computer has recreated Felix
Pi电脑重新创建了Felix
Baumgartner's record-breaking skydive
鲍姆加特纳创纪录的 跳伞
mr. Baumgartner made the furthest
先生。鲍姆加特纳做得最远
freefall in October of 2012 from a
从 2012年10月自由落体
balloon almost 39 kilometers which is 24
气球差不多39公里，这 是 24
miles high now remember that a bear
英里高现在记得那只熊
called Babbage has now left from a
所谓的巴贝奇现在已经离开了
similar height after ascending beneath a
相似的高度 在a 之后 上升
hydrogen-filled balloon the Raspberry Pi
充满氢气的树莓派气球
low-cost microcomputer inside Babbage
巴贝奇内部的低成本微电脑
transmitted his position position and
传达了他的职位和
shot Stills and video throughout the
拍摄静止图像和视频的整个
flight and sent the Raspberry Pi inside
飞行并 发送 了Raspberry Pi
the bear and his cradle switched from
熊和他的摇篮从切换
stills to video to record the moment
剧照视频录制的那一刻
when the toy fell off the computer off
当玩具掉下电脑时
the cradle sorry and started its descent
抱歉抱歉，并开始下降
on the Babbage flight the pie inside the
在巴贝奇飞行里面的馅饼
Bears body logged altitude shot footage
熊身体登录高度拍摄的 画面
and transmitted it back to the ground it
并传输回地面它
also constantly broadcast the crafts
也不断地播放工艺品
location so the flight could be mapped
所以航班可以被映射
and the pioneering toy retrieved many
而开创性的玩具很多
people follow the flight online via the
人们通过网络在线跟踪航班
streaming video feed right via the
视频流进 右经
streaming video feed sent back by
流式传输的视频反馈
Babbage I wish I could have a pie but a
巴贝奇我希望我能有一个派，但 一个
cool little bear inside my belly that
我的肚子里面的小熊很酷
sends pictures like a Google glass like
像Google的玻璃一样发送图片
a pie cherry blueberry raspberry
馅饼樱桃蓝莓覆盆子
for those of you who are listening and
对于那些正在倾听和聆听的人
don't get the visuals
不要看视觉效果
raspberry-pi referring to that little
覆盆子-pi指 这一点
micro County credit cards sighs yeah
微 县 信用卡 感叹 是啊
computer cuz I can't was ridiculous
电脑cuz我不​​能是荒谬的
things yes that's and they're all
事情是 这样的，他们都是
food-related usually silly that's cool
食物相关通常很愚蠢，很酷
that's kind of fun as a hobbyist thing
作为一个业余爱好者来说这很有趣
unfortunately I couldn't post a lot of
不幸的是我不能发布很多
pictures I'd love for you to see the
我很乐意为你们 提供 照片
pictures get onto Google or whatever
图片进入谷歌或 任何
your favorite search engine is in search
您最喜爱的搜索引擎 正在搜索中
for the guy who actually sent this up
对于实际发送这个的人来说
unfortunately he made the mistake of
不幸的是 他 犯了错误
when he posted all the pictures on
当他张贴所有的照片
Flickr he marked them as all rights
他将 Flickr 标记为 所有权利
reserved
保留的
be careful we need to have a lesson for
要小心，我们需要 有一个教训
you on how to use Flickr so that things
你就如何使用Flickr这样的东西
are Creative Commons or otherwise
是Creative Commons或其他
distributable so that I can post
可发布，以便我可以发布
pictures but his cute little teddy bear
图片，但 他可爱的小泰迪熊
he sent it up into the stratosphere and
他把它发送到平流层
then it plummeted down was he safe it
然后它跌倒了，他是安全的
didn't say if he's okay it was fine yeah
没有说 他 没事没事就好了
I saw all the pictures there on Flickr
我在Flickr上看到了所有的照片
but yeah show them on the show here's an
但是，在 这里 展示 他们的节目
feet intact yeah everything's intact and
脚完好无损， 一切都完好无损
the pictures are great
图片很棒
taking pictures all the way down and
一路下来拍照
went up further than and the guy who did
比那个 做过 的人更进一步
it last yeah teddy bear how unfair is
它最后 是泰迪熊是多么不公平
that so unfair there he is
那 是他那么不公平
ah what a cute little ah what's his back
啊 ，可爱的小 啊，他的背部是什么
but there's the computer and the I guess
但有计算机和我的猜测
it looks like double-a lithium batteries
它 看起来 像双锂电池
that they're using to power the thing
他们正在用它 来 驱动这个事物
that's kind of cool but neat that they
他们 很酷但很 整齐
were able to get loads and loads of
能够获得负载和负载
pictures mm-hmm stuff like that as well
图片mm-hmm这样的东西
well there have been some software
还有一些软件
problems at Amazon and it is now knocked
亚马逊的问题现在已经被打破了
out several high-profile websites
出几个高调的网站
including Instagram Netflix vine Airbnb
包括Instagram Netflix vine Airbnb
and several other services they were all
和他们所有的其他服务
reported being down nobody could get
据报道，没人能得到
through to the services late on Sunday
直到星期天晚上的服务
all of them rely on servers provided as
所有这些都依赖于提供的服务器
part of Amazon's Cloud Services and the
亚马逊的云服务和云的 一部分
problems were traced to a data center in
问题被追踪到数据中心
Northern Virginia that was struggling to
北弗吉尼亚 这 是 疲于
keep up with the load after the problems
跟上的问题后负荷
were resolved Amazon simply said that
亚马逊简单地表示这一点
the glitch was caused by a partial
这个故障是由部分原因造成的
failure this is a quote partial failure
失败这 是一个报价部分失败
of an
一个
networking device and that's all they
网络设备，这就是他们
said Wow it's very descriptive leave it
说哇这是非常描述性的 离开它
up to speculation yeah it was just a
直到猜测是啊，它只是一个
partial failure it wasn't a complete
部分失败是不完整的
failure big deal
失败重大
it's like me the short-lived problems
这就像我短暂的问题
come less than a week after Amazon North
在亚马逊 北方 之后不到一周
America's web store was in fact down for
美国的网上商店 实际上停机
about 30 minutes I can't buy a lot of
大约30分钟 我 不能买很多
stuff if you're started down I wonder if
如果 东西 你开始走上 不知
that affected us did anybody have any
影响我们的人有没有人
trouble getting onto our website on
麻烦进入我们的 网站
Sunday because our website is majorly
星期天，因为我们的网站是主要的
intertwined with Amazon and incidentally
与亚马逊和偶然交织在一起
on Saturday Sunday is when I had
星期六的星期天是我的时候
transitioned some of the video
过渡了一些视频
distributions so I'll bet you we took
所以我敢打赌 你我们拿走了
out their data center it's happened
他们的数据中心已经发生了
before not on Amazon boy oh boy can you
之前不在 亚马逊男孩哦，男孩可以
imagine the scale of the data that would
想象中的数据的比例那 会
have to be going through there in order
必须按顺序经过那里
to take down someone as big as Amazon
取下来 的人一样大的亚马逊
well I mean Netflix is using them to
我的意思是Netflix正在使用它们
power their service Netflix so that's
为他们的服务 Netflix 供电
got to tell you something about the
必须告诉你一些关于
scale of this caddy huge huge I think
这个球童的 规模巨大， 我认为
though if at least if our website was
尽管如果至少如果我们的网站是
down on a day like that mm-hmm and then
倒在这样的 MM-HMM，然后 每天
people go on to Netflix and Amazon and
人们去 Netflix和亚马逊
Instagram and really oh everybody's down
Instagram和真的哦，大家都失望了
yeah then they think it was themselves
是的，那么他们认为这是他们自己
right yes it must be a DNS problem yeah
对， 是的， 它 必须 是一个DNS问题 是的
all right
好吧
hey what else have we got oh this one's
嘿我们 还有什么我们 有 这个哦
interesting
有趣
oh that does look cool there are ticker
哦，看起来 很酷有股票
tape machines on there invented in 1867
1867年发明的磁带机
ever used to print stock market data
曾用于打印股市数据
arriving via Telegraph some of the
通过电报到达一些
original machines are now considered to
原来的机器现在被认为是
be a high-value antiques mm-hmm a web
是一个 高价值的古董毫米嗯网
developer from Cumbria has built a
来自坎布里亚郡的开发者已经建立了一个
modern version of a 19th century ticker
现代版19世纪的自动收报机
tape machine which prints out tweets
打印出推文的磁带机
requiring no ink and no computer so
不需要墨水，也不需要电脑
pretty cool web developer and history
很酷的Web开发人员和历史
enthusiast Adam Vaughn created his own
爱好者Adam Vaughn创造了他自己的
version of the antiquated device which
陈旧的 设备 版本
taps into Twitter and prints out tweets
点击Twitter并打印出推文
as they are posted he says the Twitter
当他们发布时，他说Twitter
tape device has build from was built
磁带设备已 建成
from scratch he's in second
从头开始， 他排在第二位
parts from clocks and other sources the
从钟表和其他来源的零件
wooden base hides a thermal printer and
木制底座隐藏热敏打印机和
a microcontroller the device connects
该设备连接的微控制器
over Ethernet and checks for new tweets
通过以太网 并检查新的推文
on his account every 30 seconds but he
在他的账户上每隔30秒，但他
hopes to eventually add support for
希望最终 加入支持
printing based on hash tags or multiple
基于散列标签或多个打印
accounts that'll be neat that's pretty
帐户将会很整齐，非常漂亮
cool I would much rather read not that I
酷我宁愿读 不是我
have my Twitter setup but it would be so
有我的推特设置，但 它会是这样的
cool what are you doing oh just redo
很酷你在做什么哦只是重做
play let me check yeah I wonder how much
玩让我 检查一下， 我想知道 多少
paper you would go through on a popular
你会通过流行的纸张
channel yikes let's hope that you don't
频道 yikes 让我们希望 你不要
Dakota like all of a sudden get tons and
达科他 突然变得像吨和
tons of people using the hashtag that's
使用 这 包括 hashtag 吨的 人
kind of neat oh and I wonder how long
那种整洁 哦 ，我想知道多久
it's gonna take before they show up
它们会在它们出现之前发生
something like that on warehouse 13 like
这样 的 事情 在仓库13中的相同
doesn't it look like something that you
它看起来不像 你的 东西 吗？
know they could they could easily using
知道他们可以轻松使用
that cool stuff I think that's pretty
那很酷的东西，我觉得很漂亮
neat I'd buy one I would definitely buy
整齐我会买一个 我肯定会买
one if it was for sale for a reasonable
一个如果它是为了一个合理的销售
price like $20 $20 and we'll throw in
价格像 20美元20美元，我们会投入
this Ginsu knife say no to Windows 8 I
这个Ginsu刀对Windows 8 I说不
simply just read the picture I figure
只是简单地读 我 的 数字 图片
that's probably know it's not your
这可能知道这不是你的
slogan that is what Germany is saying
这就是德国所说的口号
this week but on another story popular
本周，但另一个故事 流行
benchmarking site HW bot org has in fact
基准站点HW bot机构实际上已经
banned Windows 8 records from its
禁止Windows 8的 记录
benchmarks they've also discredited
基准他们也不信任
previously submitted benchmarks after
之前提交的基准
noticing an issue with the way Windows 8
注意到Windows 8的问题
tells time the simplest thing in the
讲述时间的最简单的事情在
world the real-time clock in your
世界 在你 的实时 时钟
computer you may or may not know this
电脑你可能会或可能不知道这一点
it's a chip built into your motherboard
这是你的主板内置的芯片
it's powered by a little battery so if
它是由一个小电池供电，所以如果
the power goes out or you turn off your
电源熄灭或者你 关掉了 你的电源
computer the clock still keeps time
电脑时钟仍然保持时间
Microsoft said we're not gonna go with
微软表示我们不会一起去
that we're gonna build our own unlike
我们要建立自己的不同
software clocks which can be easily
软件时钟可以 很容易
hacked and changed by software the
黑客攻击并通过软件更改
hardware clock of course is able to keep
硬件时钟当然是可以保留的
accurate time but Windows is one OS to
准确的时间，但Windows是一个 操作系统
rule them all kind of mentality has made
统治他们所有的心态
you know they want to bring their
你知道他们想要带上他们的
software Windows 8 to device
软件Windows 8到设备
which don't have hardware clocks so they
不具有硬件时钟，使他们
built it differently when the CPU base
在CPU基础上以不同的方式构建它
clock frequency in software is changed
软件中的时钟频率发生改变
after boot up here's the problem it has
开机后，这是它的问题
a huge effect on Windows 8 ability to
对Windows 8能力的巨大影响
keep accurate time as an example in
以准确的时间为例
their tests having down clock to test
他们的测试有时钟测试
CPU by about 6 percent Windows 8 lost 18
大约6％的 CPU Windows 8损失了18
seconds over just 5 minutes
仅需5分钟
when overclocked go in the opposite
当超频进入对面时
direction Windows 8 was 18 seconds ahead
方向Windows 8提前了18秒
of time overclocking roughly 4% after
超过大约 4％ 的时间 后
only 2 minutes they were off Windows 8
只有2分钟 他们离开了Windows 8
was off by 3 seconds and it would
被关了3秒，它会
progressively get worse and worse so for
逐步得到每况愈下 所以
now HW bots will block any seemingly out
现在的HW 机器人将会阻止任何 貌似出局的事物
of line windows 8 based benchmark
基于Windows 8的基准测试
results and it also is blocking all
结果，它也阻止了所有
windows 8 based benchmark records even
甚至 基于Windows 8的基准测试记录
if the score seems in line with
如果得分看起来符合
expectations so there you have it what
期望， 所以你有它
do you think of that
你有没有想到这一点
just say no obviously telling it's Logan
只是说 不明显告诉它是Logan
anyways not say no to Windows 8 it's
反正不对Windows 8说不
like the opposite of thank you at least
至少感谢你的反面
now we've got something but they get
现在我们有了一些东西， 但他们得到了
that printed on a t-shirt if somebody
如果有人 印在T恤上
comes up to you and says oh I'm thinking
来到你身边，说哦，我在想
about switching to Windows 8 what do you
关于 切换 到Windows 8你有什么
think that's like do you like do you
认为这就像你喜欢你
like to tell time what time is it you'd
想告诉时间是几点
say it's let me check not why let me
说这是让我检查不是为什么让我
check my phone and they pull out their
检查我的手机，他们拔出 他们
phone and they say well it's 751 see is
电话，他们说 这是751看到的
it because if you were running Windows 8
这是因为如果你正在运行Windows 8
on that not it would be wrong see how we
在这不是这将 是错误的看我们如何
listed that story into something that it
上市这个故事到 的东西， 它
really wasn't so just say no right you
真的不是 那么说 不对 你
can get the full stories at category 5
可以获得第 5 类的全部故事
tvs flash newsroom this week the
电视 本周闪动新闻编辑室
category 5 TV newsroom is research by
第5类电视新闻编辑室正在研究
Roy W Nash with contributions by our
罗伊W纳什与我们的贡献
community of viewers if you have a news
如果你有新闻，那么观众群体
story you think is worthy of honor
故事，你 觉得是值得 的 荣誉
mentioned you can email
提到你可以发邮件
that newsroom at category five TV for
该编辑部 在 五类 电视
the category five TV newsroom I'm
我是 五类 电视新闻编辑室
crystal wells its Christa I've been I've
克里斯塔 水晶 井我一直是我的
been working hard on developing new
一直在努力 开发新的
software have you I love coding I'm like
软件有你我喜欢编码我喜欢
I know well like when you sit down and
我很清楚你坐下来的时候
you know when you're when you create
你知道你什么时候 创作
something graphically and it feels
图形 和感觉
really good to create yes so for me
真的很好为我 创造是的
coding is that yeah so writing programs
编码是这样写的程序
that nobody else has done or that I'm
别人没做，或者 我
doing better than someone else really
比别人真的做得更好
feels like exciting to me so I've been
对我来说感觉很激动， 所以我一直这样
building new transcoders for the show
为展会搭建新的代码转换器
and what that means is that file sizes
这意味着文件大小
for your RSS feeds and for distribution
为您的RSS新闻和分发
on our website everything is going down
在我们的网站上一切都在下降
but quality is going up so strangely
但质量正在变得 如此奇怪
enough you're able to get a file that is
足够你能够得到一个文件
smaller but it's better quality so it's
规模较小，但它是更好的质量，这是
faster downloads better quality less
更快的下载质量更好 少
bandwidth usage and all that kind of
带宽使用和所有这些
stuff so I'm thinking specifically of
东西，所以我特别想到
people who are in the military and you
在 军队 和你的人
know maybe don't have access to really
知道，也许用不上 真的
good high-speed Internet and so we
良好的高速互联网，所以我们
created a new LD transcoder which is low
创建了一个低的新LD转码器
definition but get this an mp3 of the
定义， 但得到 这个 MP3的
entire episode of category 5 is about 60
类别5的整个情节大约是60
Meg's
梅格
right the full hour including video and
整整一小时，包括 视频和
audio being able to watch it in a
音频能够 在a中 观看
quality that is reasonable enough is
质量是 不够合理的
only 50 Meg's ah so anyway so this is
只有50梅格的啊 所以无论如何这 是
something that I've been experimenting
我一直在尝试的东西
with and we're gonna be seeing that over
有 和我们要去是在看
the next couple weeks so if you notice
接下来的 几周，所以如果你注意到
some changes in quality it's probably
可能会改变质量
just me tinkering around with the new
只是我在修补新的东西
transcoders but really exciting stuff
代码转换器，但真的很刺激的东西
really exciting to to see what you know
真的很令人兴奋，看看你知道什么
what that's going to do for our viewers
这将为我们的观众 做什么
I've always been working toward we've
我一直在为我们努力
been working on it for a couple years
一直在努力了 几年
now getting the show really readily
现在很容易得到演出
available in mainland China it's really
在中国大陆可以买到
tough because of the Great Firewall of
因为美国的防火墙很艰难
China and so we have basically created
中国等基本上已经 创建
this whole system with that in the back
这整个系统在后面
of my mind to completely avoid any of
我的想法完全避免 任何
that blockage or so everybody's gonna
这堵塞或大家的要去
have access to this is gonna be fast
有机会获得 这个 会很快
it's gonna be the best that we've ever
这将是我们有史以来最好的
had and it's gonna be just in time for
有，它会 准时
season 7 which is starting at the end of
第七季即将 开始
next month so
下个月如此
pretty exciting and it's all content
非常令人兴奋， 这是所有的内容
distribution so it's all done through
所以这一切都是 通过 完成
Amazon who hopefully they'll stay online
亚马逊希望他们会保持在线
all the time all the time that would be
所有的 时间 所有的 时间，这 将 是
helpful
有帮助
hey do we have some viewer questions I'd
嘿，我们有一些观众问题
love to I know we're tight for time and
爱我知道我们对时间紧张和
everybody who is here with us and for
大家谁在这里 与我们 和
sending in your questions okay all right
在您的问题发送没事 没事
what do you have a few here question
这里有几个问题你有什么问题
from Xavier hey Xavier it says hi there
来自Xavier hey Xavier 它在那里说你好
first of all I would like to streaming a
首先 我想流一个
real event from a venue I would like to
我想 从一个场地举办真正的活动
stream a real event for venue therefore
因此流出场地的真实事件
I would like to ask your help to find
我想问你的帮助 找到
out how this would work
了解这将如何工作
okay I would like to use two different
好吧我想 用两种不同的
cameras and only software solution
相机和只有软件解决方案
acceptable for the encoding and for
可接受的编码和
video mixing as well sure I I have a Sat
视频混合，以及确保 II有一个星期六
uplink satellite internet so it's
上行卫星互联网，所以它
reasonably fast but not very fast it's
相当快的，但不是非常快 这是
always looking for some programs that
一直在寻找一些程序 ，
you could use to achieve as goals an SDI
你可以用它 来实现 SDI的 目标
s video or fire okay shall use that
那么视频或火灾可以 使用
those are different kinds of cameras
那些是不同种类的相机
yeah SDI and firewire s-video are
是的SDI 和火线的S-Video 是
different interfaces for the capture
不同的 捕捉界面
device so firewire being a digital
设备如此firewire是一个 数字
standard but it's SD it's a really low
标准， 但它是SD它是一个非常低
quality 720 by 480 if I recall so the
如果我 回忆如此，质量720 480
equivalent of DVD quality which you
相当于你的DVD质量
think is really really high because DVDs
认为 真的很高，因为DVD
look good but in fact an SD camera in
看起来不错，但实际上是一台SD摄像机
the same resolution is not going to turn
同样的决议不会转变
out very impressive video unless you've
除非你拥有非常令人印象深刻的视频
got a two to three thousand dollar
得到了两三千美元
camera but if you're gonna spend that
相机， 但如果你会花这一点
kind of money and as well buy an HD
一些钱，以及购买高清
camera and they're gonna get way better
相机， 他们会变得更好
quality anyways depending on your budget
质量取决于 你的预算
and that's a big loaded question because
这是一个很大的问题， 因为
you're asking me okay well what do I
你问我好吗我该怎么做
need I would suggest you get two cat
需要我会建议你得到 两只猫
five dot TV slash Wirecast it's the
五点电视 斜线Wirecast它是
software that we use I tried doing this
我们使用我试图做这个软件
last week can I do this right now Krista
上周我可以现在就做这个 克里斯塔
can we smile just for for our viewers
我们可以微笑只为我们的观众
aver who is asking this question I'm
谁问我这个问题
gonna try to take a screen shot so you
会尝试拍摄 一个屏幕截图， 让你
can see what this actually looks like to
可以看到这实际上看起来 像
us so smile for the camera
我们对相机微笑
how's that did I get it so Xavier what
我是怎么得到它的？ Xavier是怎么回事？
this software does now I'm really
这个软件现在确实是我真的
quickly gonna go into GIMP and dry
很快就会进入GIMP并 干燥
pasting because what happened last week
粘贴，因为上周发生了什么
is then when we copied the show notes
那么当我们复制演出笔记
and everything at it over wrote the
并在它的一切 写 了
clipboard so we're gonna get at this
剪贴板， 所以我们会得到这个
time folks you're gonna have a
时间伙计， 你会有一个
screenshot of a live broadcast of
现场直播的 截图
category-five from within
从 内部 五类
Wirecast we got it yes okay Pence's I do
Wirecast 我们得到了它 是 好的便士的我做的
look pensive they're interesting it's
看起来很沉闷， 他们很有趣
probably thinking about how I could get
可能想想我该如何 得到
the screenshot so with Wirecast it's
这是Wirecast的截图
software and you can plug in as many
软件，你 可以插入尽可能 多的软件
cameras as your computer can handle but
相机作为你的电脑可以处理，但
here's the thing the more cameras that
这里的东西更多的相机， 这些 相机
you have the more power you need
你有更多的权力，你需要
you asked about firewire so I'm going to
你问火线所以我要去
suggest ya go that route give it a try
建议你去那条路线试试看
and get cheap little firewire cameras I
并获得廉价的小火线相机我
wish I could reach one I can see one
希望我能达到我能看到的一个
right there we used to use them they
就在那里，我们曾经使用它们
were okay they did okay for a live event
没关系， 他们没有为 现场比赛 做好准备
they work great you can run them off of
他们的工作很好，你 可以从他们运行
a laptop and it will still work
一台笔记本电脑，它 仍然会工作
fantastically well because it's low
非常好，因为它很低
resolution you're not gonna get HD
分辨率， 你不会得到高清
quality but you're gonna get fair enough
质量， 但你会变得足够公平
quality it's gonna work really well
它的质量会非常好
because there's not a lot of CPU
因为没有太多 的 CPU
overhead on an SD camera as soon as you
尽快在SD相机上开销
jump into HD you need power and a lot of
跳进高清 你需要电力和很多
it for us to run three cameras it takes
它为 我们运行需要三个摄像头
a whole lot of power it takes a computer
一台电脑 需要 大量的 电力
that is dreadfully heavy to carry around
这是可怕沉重的携带
you wouldn't want to use it for live
你不会希望将它 用于实况
venues because to move it around is just
由于场地周围移动， 这 只是
unbelievably heavy SDI is another good
难以置信的重度SDI是另一好事
option if you want to get a deck link
选项， 如果你想 获得甲板链接
card from Blackmagic designs you can get
来自Blackmagic设计的卡可以获得
all that stuff from cat5 dot TV /bh but
所有这些东西从cat5 dot TV / bh 但是
you know I I don't know what else to say
你知道我不知道 还有什么 要说的
Wirecast has a great forum a community
Wirecast有一个很棒 的社区 论坛
where you can get in there depending on
在那里你可以进入那里 取决于
whether you're gonna be running Windows
你是否会运行Windows
or Mac get in to the appropriate forum
或Mac进入适当的 论坛
for Telestream Wirecast and just follow
用于Telestream Wirecast， 然后关注
the links and when you're there ask the
链接和当你在那里问问
question there are some very helpful
问题有一些非常有帮助
people in the community such as Craig
克雷格 等社区人士
ass and Craig will gladly point you in
屁股和克雷格会很高兴地 指点你
the right direction and I suggest that
正确的方向，我建议
because that's what they do we utilize
因为这是 他们做 什么 ，我们利用
the software we utilize the technology
我们利用该技术 的软件
we have been here long enough I mean
我的意思是我们在这里已经够久了
we're coming up on our seventh year
我们在第七年即将到来
we're in our seventh year and
我们在我们的第七个年头，并
and so you know I've been around the
所以你知道我一直在 这里
block enough times to know how to do it
阻止足够的 时间来 知道如何去做
but to you there might be specifics that
但对你来说 可能有这样的细节
you are looking for so lighting is key
你正在 寻找照明是关键
lighting is very very important for live
照明对于现场非常重要
broadcasting we are blinded by the
广播我们被蒙蔽了
lights that we have here in the studio
灯光， 我们在这里在工作室
it's true I come out with a bit of a tan
这是真的，我出来一点点 晒黑
afterwards I absolutely do
事后我 绝对会这样做
yeah yeah I haven't even been in the Sun
是啊是啊 我还没有过在 阳光 下
this year and yet you can see I've got
今年，但你可以看到我有
this farmer's tan going on yeah just
这个农民的棕褐色只是在继续
from these lights because I'm here every
从这些灯，因为我在这里每一个
Tuesday night for an hour so good luck
周二晚上 好一个小时好运气
hope that helps it's a loaded question
希望能帮助它是一个加载的问题
my friend email me if you want more if
我的朋友给我发电子邮件，如果你想要更多
you want to just chat and we'll just go
你只想聊天，我们就走
back and forth together what else we got
一起来回我们还有什么
do we're literally out of time do we
我们是否真的 在时间之外
have time I just oh I'm so sorry folks
有时间我只是哦，我很抱歉的 人
that I'm that I've talked so much that
我是说我已经说过这么 多 ，
I've talked too much
我说得太多了
I hope that you've enjoyed yourself
我希望你喜欢你自己
knowing that it's been fun then I had
知道它很有趣，然后 我有
fun I had yeah yeah so if I had fun they
有趣的我是 耶，所以如果我有乐趣他们
had if she had fun fantastic she even
如果她甚至有乐趣的话，她会有
learned to back up at first he's so
最初学会了备份，他是如此
proud like a proud mom I finally got
骄傲得像我 终于得到的 一位骄傲的妈妈
folks have a fantastic week next week
人们下周会有一个精彩的一周
aired kid is gonna be joining me we're
一个孩子会 加入我们，我们是
gonna be taking a look at some of these
会看看其中 的一些
really cool devices from Rico magic
来自Rico 魔术的非常酷的设备
we've got this MK 602 we're gonna be
我们有这个MK 602我们会
taking a look at oh yes sits atop your
看看哦，是坐在你的上面
television and turns it into a Skype
电视并将其变成Skype
video communications unit we've got all
视频通信部门，我们拥有了所有的
that stuff the 802 for the the 702 to
这些东西的802为702， 以
remote control the dreamiest remote for
遥控最梦幻的遥控器
your HTPC it all comes to you from Rico
你的HTPC都来自Rico
Magic we're gonna be looking at it next
魔术我们 会在接下来看看它
week
周
with Eric kits so thanks a lot for being
与埃里克 包，所以非常感谢你的 存在
here with us thanks Krista thank you
我们在这里感谢克里斯塔谢谢你
fantastic week see it
美妙的一周看到它
we hope you enjoy the show
我们希望你喜欢这个节目
category 5 TV broadcasts live from
5类电视直播
Barrie Ontario Canada every Tuesday at
每周二在加拿大安大略省巴里市
7:00 p.m. Eastern if you're watching
东部 时间晚上7:00， 如果你正在观看
this on demand or through cable TV check
这 需求或通过有线电视检查
out the local show times in your area at
在你所在地区 的当地 演出时间
category-five TV and find out when you
五类电视，并找出你的时间
can watch live and interact in the
可以观看 现场直播和互动
community chat room category 5 is a
社区聊天室类别 5是一个
production of prodigy digital solutions
生产神童数字解决方案
and is licensed under Creative Commons
并获得知识共享许可
Attribution 2.5 Canada we'll see you
归属地 2.5 加拿大， 我们会看到你
next time thanks for tuning in
下次 感谢 调整